export const examNumber1 = [
    {
      id: 1,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_1",
      question: "Question_Label_1",
      options: ["Ques_1_Option_Label_1", "Ques_1_Option_Label_2", "Ques_1_Option_Label_3", "Ques_1_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_1_Option_Label_2",
      selectedAnswer: null,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_2",
      question: "Question_Label_2",
      options: ["Ques_2_Option_Label_1", "Ques_2_Option_Label_2", "Ques_2_Option_Label_3", "Ques_2_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_2_Option_Label_3",
      selectedAnswer: null,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_3",
      question: "Question_Label_3",
      options: ["Ques_3_Option_Label_1", "Ques_3_Option_Label_2", "Ques_3_Option_Label_3", "Ques_3_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_2_Option_Label_4",
      selectedAnswer: null,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_4",
      question: "Question_Label_4",
      options: ["Ques_4_Option_Label_1", "Ques_4_Option_Label_2", "Ques_4_Option_Label_3", "Ques_4_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_2_Option_Label_4",
      selectedAnswer: null,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_5",
      question: "Question_Label_5",
      options: ["Ques_5_Option_Label_1", "Ques_5_Option_Label_2", "Ques_5_Option_Label_3", "Ques_5_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_2_Option_Label_4",
      selectedAnswer: null,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_6",
      question: "Question_Label_6",
      options: ["Ques_6_Option_Label_1", "Ques_6_Option_Label_2", "Ques_6_Option_Label_3", "Ques_6_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_2_Option_Label_3",
      selectedAnswer: null,
    },
  ]
  export const examNumber1Answer = [
    {
      id: 1,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_1",
      question: "Question_Label_1",
      options: ["Ques_1_Option_Label_1", "Ques_1_Option_Label_2", "Ques_1_Option_Label_3", "Ques_1_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_1_Option_Label_2",
      selectedAnswer: "Ques_1_Option_Label_1",
      answerBrief: "AnswerBrief_Label_1"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_2",
      question: "Question_Label_2",
      options: ["Ques_2_Option_Label_1", "Ques_2_Option_Label_2", "Ques_2_Option_Label_3", "Ques_2_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_2_Option_Label_3",
      selectedAnswer: "Ques_2_Option_Label_2",
      answerBrief: "AnswerBrief_Label_1"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_3",
      question: "Question_Label_3",
      options: ["Ques_3_Option_Label_1", "Ques_3_Option_Label_2", "Ques_3_Option_Label_3", "Ques_3_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_3_Option_Label_4",
      selectedAnswer: "Ques_3_Option_Label_4",
      answerBrief: "AnswerBrief_Label_1"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_4",
      question: "Question_Label_4",
      options: ["Ques_4_Option_Label_1", "Ques_4_Option_Label_2", "Ques_4_Option_Label_3", "Ques_4_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_4_Option_Label_4",
      selectedAnswer: "Ques_4_Option_Label_2",
      answerBrief: "AnswerBrief_Label_1"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_5",
      question: "Question_Label_5",
      options: ["Ques_5_Option_Label_1", "Ques_5_Option_Label_2", "Ques_5_Option_Label_3", "Ques_5_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_5_Option_Label_4",
      selectedAnswer: "Ques_5_Option_Label_4",
      answerBrief: "AnswerBrief_Label_1"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      questionLabel: "QuestionLabel_6",
      question: "Question_Label_6",
      options: ["Ques_6_Option_Label_1", "Ques_6_Option_Label_2", "Ques_6_Option_Label_3", "Ques_6_Option_Label_4"],
      correctAnswer: "Ques_6_Option_Label_3",
      selectedAnswer: "Ques_6_Option_Label_4",
      answerBrief: "AnswerBrief_Label_1"
    },
  ]